Guide to the Robert Hofstadter Papers SC0426
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1992-097
  - "CaI and CaI2 (Eu) Scintillation Crystals", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - "Electron Scattering by Calcium at 250 MeV (France)", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Nucleon Structure (book) (empty folder), undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - "Some Thoughts on the Growth of High Energy Physics," Scintillation and Semiconductor Counter Symposium speech, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - "Electromagnetic Form Factors of the Proton and Neutron," HEPL report no. 344, reprinted from Nucleon Structure, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - "Cryogenic Targets for Electron Scattering," HEPL report no. 343, reprinted from Nucleon Structure, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - "Electron Scattering in Tritium and Helium-3," HEPL report no. 342, reprinted from Nucleon Structure, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - "An Analysis of Tritium and Helium-3 Form Factors," HEPL report no. 346, reprinted from Nucleon Structure, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - "Neutron Form Factors from Inelastic Electron-Deuteron Scattering", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - "Method of Study of High-Energy Scattering Events with Very Small Energy Loss," HEPL report no. 332, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - "Inelastic Electron-Deuteron Scattering Experiments and Nucleon Structure," HEPL report no. 321, also published in Physical Review, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - "Neutron Charge Form Factor from Tritium and Helium-3 Analysis," HEPL report no. 325, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - "Electron Scattering on Nucleons; Three-Body Nuclei, and Ca40," HEPL report no. 355, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - "Electron Scattering by Calcium at 250 MeV," HEPL report no. 347, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - "Electron Scattering on Nucleons and Nuclei," HEPL report no. 361, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Pavoda Acceptance Speech, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - "Elastic Electron Scattering from Tritium and Helium-3," HEPL report no. 336, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - "Elastic Electron Scattering from Tritium and Helium-3," HEPL report no. 338, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - "Recent High Energy Electron Investigations at Stanford University," HEPL report no. 383, Springer Tactics in Modern Physics vol. 39, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - "Neutron," World Book Encyclopeida, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - "Inelastic Electron Spectra from the Electrodisintegration of Deuterium", 1965 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - "Neutron Form Factors from Inelastic Electron-Deuteron Scattering", 1965 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - "Neutron Form Factors from Inelastic Electron-Deuteron Scattering," HEPL Report no. 360, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - "Scattering and the Pionic Form Factor," HEPL Report no. 368, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - "Toward a More Scientific Medicine", 1965 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - "Charge Distribution of Ca40 and Ca44 from 250 MeV Electron Scattering," HEPL Report no. 411, also published in Physical Review Letters, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - "High Energy Work at Stanford", 1965 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - "Upper Limit of the Electron’s Electric Dipole Moment," HEPL Report no. 333, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - "Elastic Electron Scattering from Tritium and Helium-3" (empty folder), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - "Neutron Form Factors from Inelastic Electron-Deuteron Scattering", undated (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - "Proton Form Factors from Elastic Electron-Proton Scattering," HEPL Report no. 359, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - "Isotope Effect In Ca40, Ca44, and Ca48 Charge Distributions from 250 MeV Elastic Electron Scattering," Physical Review Letters, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - "Neutron Form Factors from a Study of Inelastic Electron Spectra in the Electrodisintegration of Deuterium," HEPL report no. 420, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - "Neutron Form Factors from Inelastic Electron Scattering in Tritium and He3," HEPL Report no. 443, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - "The Smallest Thing in the Universe" (folder originally unnumbered), undated (Box 2, Folder 180.1)
  - "Scattering of Fast Electrons by Oriented Ho165 Nuclei," HEPL Report no. 448, also published in Physical Review Letters, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - "Charge Distributions of the CA40 and CA48 Isotope", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - "The Instant Electorate," Convocation Address, Carlton University, Ottawa, ON, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - "Experimental Results on the Charge Distributions of Calcium Isotopes", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - "An Interpretation of Pb208 Electron Scattering Data", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - "Scattering of 750 MeV Electrons by Calcium Isotopes," HEPL Report no. 522, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - "Nuclear Radii Determined by Electron Scattering Methods", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - "A Lead Floride Cerenkov Shower Counter", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - "Energy Loss and Straggling of High Energy Muons in NaI(Tl)," Physical Review, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - APS Abstract, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 189a)
  - "Nuclear Charge Density Distributions", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - "Letter to Dr. Jerome Fregeau", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 190a)
  - "Calcium Iodide Phosphors," U.S. Patent 3,303,342, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 190b)
  - "Search for Fractionally Charged Particles," HEPL Report no. 512, also published in Physical Review, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - "Electron Induced Fission in U238, Bi209, and Ta181", 1968 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - "Total Absorption Detectors for High Energy Physics," HEPL Report no. 561, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - "A High Energy y-Ray Detector with Good Resolution," Review of Scientific Instruments, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - "A Lead Fluoride Cerenkov Shower Counter," HEPL Report no. 550, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - "A NaI(Tl) Spectrometer for y-Rays In The GEV Range," HEPL report no. 551, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - "A Possible Aid to Government Foreign Policy," San Angelo State College address, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - "Total Absorption Nuclear Cascade Detectors for High Energy Physics," HEPL Report no. 556, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - "The Relation of the Weizmann Institute to Pure Science," talk delivered in Milwaukee, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - "Electron Scattering Studies of Calcium and Titanium Isotopes," HEPL report no. 554, also published in Physical Review, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - "Electron Scattering Studies of Ca40 and Ca48", 1968 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - "The Atomic Accelerator," HEPL Report no. 560, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - "New Detectors for High and Super-High Energy Physics," HEPL Report no. 572, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - "New Detectors for High and Super High Energy Physics" (empty folder), undated (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - "Electron and Bremsstrahlung-Induced Fission of Heavy and Medium-Heavy Nuclei," Physical Review, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - "Problems of High Energy Gamma-Ray and Particle Detection", 1969 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - "NaI(Tl) Total Absorption Detector for Electrons and y-Rays at GeV Energies," Nature, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - "New Detectors for High Energy Physics," HEPL Report no. 599, also published in Science Magazine, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - "Electron Scattering," HEPL Report no. 602 (empty folder), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - "Generation of Mechanical Vibrations by Penetrating Particles," Physical Review Letters, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - "On the Design of NaI(Tl) Total Absorption Detectors for Strongly Interacting Particles at GeV Energies," Nuclear Instruments and Methods, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - "Proton Halo In Calcium," photocopy of abstract with notes, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - "Elastic Electron Scattering by Pb208 and New Information About the Nuclear Charge Distribution," HEPL Report no. 613, also published in Physical Review Letters, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - "A Measurement of K2+/- Nucleus Total Cross Sections", 1969 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - "Total Absorption Detectors for High and Super-High Energy Physics," HEPL Report no. 599, also published in Science Magazine, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Physics and Man Lecture: "Discovery and Consequences -- a personal experience," draft, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - "A New Instrument Concept for Gamma-Ray Asronomy," IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science, 12th Scintillation and Semiconductor Counter Symposium, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - "Properties Of A NaI(Tl) Total Absorption Spectrometer for Electrons," IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science, 12th Scintillation and Semiconductor Counter Symposium, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - "Mechanical Oscillations Induced by Penetrating Particles," IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science, 12th Scintillation and Semiconductor Counter Symposium, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - "A High Z Scintillator," IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science, 12th Scintillation and Semiconductor Counter Symposium, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - "Fine Structure in Nuclear Charge Distribution", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - "Suggested Device for Precise Measurement of Particle Trajectories," HEPL Report no. 607, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - "Elastic Electron and Muon Scattering at 100 MeV", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - "Total Absorption Detector," Encyclopedia of Science and Technology, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - "Total Absorption Detectors for Super-High Energy Physics," HEPL Report no. 634, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - "Tests on Total Absorption Detectors at NAL", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - "Measurement of Cross Sections for X-Ray Production by High-Energy Electrons," HEPL Report no. 618, also published in Physical Review A, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - "Request for Parasite Time In The Neutral Ko Beam In End Station B" (empty folder), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - "A Proposed Spectrometer for Stanford’s High Energy Physics Laboratory," HEPL Report no. 633, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - "New Methods of Detection of High Energy Particles", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - (folder not present) (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - "Nuclear Charge Distributions from Electron Scattering Barium and Neodymium," HEPL Report no. 641, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - "Response of Activated Thallium Chloride as a Scintillation Spectrometer for High Energy Electrons", 1971 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - "The Superconducting Linear Accelerator at Stanford", 1971 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - "Detectors for High Energy Physics," Lindau Lake Conference, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - "Recirculation of an Electron Bean in a Linear Accelerator," HEPL Report no. 664, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - "Experiment on Inclusive Production of High-Energy Neutral Pions and Gamma-Rays in Pion-Proton Interactions" (empty folder), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - "Performance of a Thallium Chloride Scintillator as a Total Absorption Shower Cascade Detector", 1972 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - "Properties and Applications of Large NaI (Tl) Total Absorption Spectrometers," HEPL Report no. 672, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - "Electron-Scattering Determination of Isotopic Differences in the Charge Distributions of Ti46, 48, 50," HEPL Report no. 676, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - "High Energy Physics Using Total Absorption Detectors", 1972 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - "Total Absorption Detectors and Their Applications to High Energy Physics", 1972 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - "Inclusive Production of High-Energy Neutral Pions from Pion-Production Collisions at 14 GeV/c", 1973 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Congressional Testimony (statement to Subcommittee on Space Science and Applications on the subject of NASA's physics and astronomy program), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - "Recent Applications of NAI(Tl) Total Absorption Counters," HEPL Report no. 712, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - "Total Absorption Detectors and Their Applications to High Energy Physics" (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - "An Experiment to Measure the Reactions e+e- -->e+e- -->2y and e+e- --> u+u- at Spear," HEPL Report no. 716, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - "Gamma Ray Bursts of Cosmic Origin", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - "Measurements of e+e- -->e+e- -->yy and e+e- --> u+u- at Spear", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - "Observations of the Reactions e+e- -->e+e- -->yy and e+e- --> u+u- at Center-of-Mass Energy of 5.2. GeV", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - "Large NaI(Tl) Crystals as High Resolution Spectrometers in High Energy Physics in Gamma Ray Astronomy," HEPL Report no. 745, also published in IEEE Transactions, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - "Twenty-Five Years of Scintillation Counting," IEEE, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - "Observations of the Reactions e+e- -->e+e- -->yy and e+e- --> u+u- at Center-of-Mass Energies close to 3105 MeV," HEPL Report no. 748, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - "Experiments in Laser Fusion", 1975 (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - "Measurements of Selected Psi (3684) Branching Ratios from a Study of Secondary Pairs," Physical Review Letters, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - "Search for Monenergentic yRays from Psi (3684) Decay," Physical Review Letters, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - "Quantum Electrodynamics in Electron-Positron Systems," HEPL Report no. 768, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - "Tests of QED from SLAC Experiments SP-4 and SP-16 at Spear," HEPL Report no. 767, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - "Laser Induced Fusion" (book) (empty folder), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - "Laser Induced Fusion" (manuscript) (empty folder), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - "Psi (3095) and Psi (3864) Results from the HEPL Experiment (SP-16) at Spear," HEPL Report no. 766, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - "Measurement of the Reaction e+e- --> yy in the Region of the Psi (3684)," HEPL Report no. 775, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Statement to Subcommittee on HUD-Independent Agencies, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - "Some Fundamental Tests of Quantum Electrodynamics," HEPL Report no. 779, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - "Recent Tests of Electrodynamics at Center of Mass Energies Close to 7.4 GeV", 1976 (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - "Measurement of the Reaction e+e- --> e+e- at the Center of Mass Energies of 7.0 and 7.4 GeV," Physical Review Letters, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - "Standinger Arbeitsausschuss Fur Die Tagungen Der Nobelpristrager In Lindau", 1976 (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - "Laser Induced Fusion", 1976 (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - "Radiative Decays of the Psi (3684) and Psi (3095)" (empty folder), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - "Preliminary Evidence for a Low-Energy Monochromatic Gamma Ray from e+e- Collisions Near S-To-The-1/2=4.2 Gev" (empty folder), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - "Collisions At 14-GeV/c" (empty folder), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - "Inclusive Production of High-Energy Neutral Pions from Pion-Proton Collisions at 14-GeV/c," Physical Review D, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - "Performance of Large, Modularized NaI(Tl) Detectors," HEPL Report no. 789, also presented at the IEEE 1976 Nuclear Science Symposium, and published in proceedings (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - "Laser Fusion", 1976 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Testimony of KMS Fusion, Inc. on Laser Fusion before the Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources, Subcommittee on Energy Research and Development, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - "Inclusive y-Ray Spectra from Psi (3095) and Psi (3684) Decays," Physical Review Letters, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - "Elastic Cross Sections for e+ 40Ca At 757.5 MeV," Physical Review C, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - "Measurements of the Reaction e+e- --> yy at Center-of-Mass Energies in the Range 6.2-7.4 GeV," HEPL Report no. 781, also published in Physical Review D, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - "Design and Performance of a Modularized NaI(Tl) Detector (The Crystal Prototype)," HEPL Report no. 801, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - "A Proposal for the Use of Crystal Ball Detector System at PEP" (empty folder), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - "Comment on Nuclear Charge Distributions of Isotone Pairs, II. 39K and 40Ca", 1977 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - "Experimental Tests of Quantum Electrodynamics through the Measurement of the Reactions e+e- --> e+e-, e+e- --> yy and e+e- --> u+u- at a Center-of-Mass Energy of 5.2 GeV*," HEPL Report no. 774, also published in Physical Review, 1977, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - "Measurements of the Reaction e+e- --> u+u- at Center-of-Mass Energies in the Range 6.2-7.4 GeV," HEPL Report no. 788, also published in Physical Review D, 1977, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - "Use of a Low Energy Proton Accelerator for Calibrating a Large NaI(Tl) Array in a High Energy Physics Experiment," HEPL Report no. 833, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - "Compact Multiwire Proportional Chambers and Electronics for the Crystal Ball Detector," HEPL Report no. 832, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - "Gamma-Ray Astrophysics -- a new look at the universe," Science Magazine, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - "Upper Limit for the Decay u+ --> e+y," Physical Review Letters, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - "On the Detection of 50 MeV y-Rays with a Large Modularized NaI(Tl) Detector", 1979 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - "The Crystal Ball Data Acquisition System", 1979 (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - "Initial Studies of the Charmonium System Using the Crystal Ball Data at SPEAR," SLAC Publication no. 2598, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - "A Large Solid Angle Neutral Detector for SPEAR II" (empty folder), undated (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - "Results from the Crystal Ball Detector at SPEAR," SLAC Publication no. 2425, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - "Recent Results from the Crystal Ball," HEPL Report no. 860, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Crystal Ball Experiment, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - "Results on Charmonium from the Crystal Ball," SLAC Publication no. 2386, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - "Characteristic of the Telescope for High Energy y-Ray Astronomy Selected for Definition Studies on the Gamma Ray Observatory," NASA publication, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - "Use of an Active Coded Collimator for Improved Directional Measurements In High Energy y-Ray Astronomy", 1979 (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - "Inorganic Scintillators," Nuclear Instruments and Methods, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - "Laser Produced Nuclear Fusion," Physics and Contemporary Needs, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - "Initial Studies of the Carmonium System Using the Crystal Ball Data at Spear," SLAC Publication no. 2598, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - "Elastic Ross Sections for E- + 48CA at 757.5 MeV," Physical Review C, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - "Decay J/Psi -- 3y and a Search for the nc," SLAC Publication no. 2430, also published in Physical Review Letters, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - "Measurement of the Decays Psi ' -->nj/Psi and Psi; ' -- > pi o j/Psi," Physical Review Letters, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - "Observation of an nc Candidate with Mass 2987+- 9 MeV," SLAC Publication no. 2578, also published in Physical Review Letters, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - "Energy from Fusion", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - "Cardmonium Studies with the Crystal Ball," SLAC Publication no. 2529, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - "e+e- Physics Near Charm Threshold via the Crystal Ball," SLAC Publication no. 2563", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - "Radiative Decays of the Psi and Psi '," SLAC Publication no. 2550, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - no folder present (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - "Production of pi0 and pi0 eta in Photon-Photon Collisions," SLAC Publication no. 2821, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - "Measurement of the Branching Ratio and Polarization for J/psi—gamma f(1270)," SLAC Publication no. 2847, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - "A Study of the Reaction PSI-prime --> gamma gamma J/PSI," SLAC Publication no.2836, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - "Measurements of Inclusive eta Production In e+e- Interactions Near Charm Threshold," SLAC Publication no. 2731, also published in Physical Review Letters, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - "Observation of an eta eta Resonance In J/psi Radiative Decays," SLAC Publication no. 2822, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - "Observation of an eta-charm-prime Candidate State with Mass 3592-MeV+- 5_MeV," SLAC Publication no. 2814, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - "Crystal Ball Evidence for New States," SLAC Publication no. 2809, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - "Recent Results from the Crystal Ball," SLAC Publication no. 2796, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - "Synchrotron Radiation and Its Application to Digital Subtraction Angiography", 1981 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - "A Search for mu+ -->e+ gamma-," Physical Review D, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - "Upper Limit for J/psi --> gamma Axion," SLAC Publication no. 2878, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - "Observation of a Pseudoscalar State at 1440-MeV in J/psi Radiative Decays," Physical Review Letters, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - "Identification of a Pseudoscalar State 1440 MeV in J/psi Radiative Decays", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - "Observation of the Radiative Decay J/psi --> gamma eta pi pi" (empty folder), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - "Implementation of Digital Subtraction Angiography with a Synchrotron X-Ray Beam", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - "Observation of an eta(C) Candidate State with Mass 3592+- 5 MeV" (empty folder), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - "A High Energy Gamma Ray Astronomy Experiment", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - "Scintillation Counter," McGraw-Hill Encyclopedia, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - "Crystal Ball at the SLC: Letter of Intent" (empty folder), undated (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - "Charmonium Spectroscopy from Inclusive Photons in J/psi and psi-Prime Decays," SLAC Publication no. 2887, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - "Possible Gluonium States In Radiative psi Decay", undated (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - "K-Edge Digital Substraction Angiography with Synchrotron X-Rays", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - "The Application of Synchrotron Radiation to Non-Invaisive Angiography," Nuclear Instruments and Methods, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - "A Precision Measurement of the Upsilon-prime Mesons Mass," Physics Letters, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 332)
  - "A New Approach to Coronary Angiography", 1983 (Box 5, Folder 333)
  - "Observation of the Production of n Mesons in Two-Photon Collisions," SLAC Publication no. 3220, also published in Physical Review D, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - "Study of Gamma-Prime Radiative Decays with the Crystal Ball at Doris" (empty folder; title may be incorrect), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 335)
  - "First Results from the Crystal Ball at Doris--II" (empty folder), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 336)
  - "Results from the Crystal Ball at Doris--II," SLAC Publication no. 3232, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 337)
  - "The Study of the Decay J/psi --> y n pi pi," Physical Review Letters, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - "Evaluation of Synchrotron X-Rays for Digital Subtraction Coronary Angiography", 1983 (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - "EGRET: The High Energy Gamma Ray Telescope for NASA's Gamma Ray Observatory" (empty folder), 1983 (Box 5, Folder 340)
  - "Thallium Halide Radiation Detectors," Proceedings of the International Conference on Nuclear Physics, Bologna, Italy, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - "Thallium Halide Radiation Detectors," Physical Review B, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - "Cross Strands Linking Physics and Medicine", 1984 (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - "Das Kristallkugel -- Experiment (The Crystal Ball Experiment)", 1984 (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - "Method and Means for Minimally Invaisive Angiography Using Mono-Chromatized Synchrotron Radiation," patent letter and copy of patent, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - "Evaluation of Synchrotron X-Rays for Tranvenous Coronary Angiography", 1984 (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - Welcoming Address, IUPAP Talk in San Francisco, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - "Upsilon Family Decays," SLAC Publication no. 3469, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - "Radiative Decays of the y(2S) Resonance," SLAC Publication no. 3325, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - "A Search for the Muon-Number Violating Decay Mu—e+e+e-," Los Alamos National Laboratory Publication LA-UR-84-2143, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - "Proposal for the Study and Development of Crystal Conduction Counters", 1984 (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - "Evidence for a Narrow Massive State in the Radiative Decays of the Upsilon," SLAC Publication no. 3380, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 352)